Hello.
In this next lecture, I want to update my health pick up so it's a bit more dynamic if we open it up.
And go over to here where we give our player character one piece of health.
Just right click on this value and promote it to a variable.
Just cool this health to give.
Then if we just make this instance editable and go compile and change this value to B two.
Now if I go compile and just close this, if I set my heart in the world, we can see that the default
health to give is to to navigate play.
And let's say I get damaged three times, my heart should heal me.
Two pieces of health.
Although when I pick up the heart, I am given two pieces of health.
Although the heart does not reflect this.
So we need to update our heart.
That way it can handle if the character receives multiple pieces of health at once.
So in order to do that, if we go back to our widget blueprint of the player HUD.
And go over to the graph.
And if we just select the show Heart custom event, we want to go to add new input and just call this
number.
Then we're going to change this variable type to be an integer.
And we just want to right click and look forward to for loop node.
Hook up number to last index and hook this up to for loop.
Then under the first index, just type in one and hook this up to loop body.
So the idea here is if we pick up two pieces of health, then we're going to make this number two and
it will run this for loop twice and then this will add two hearts to our screen.
So now go compile and go back to my health.
Pick up.
Under the so hot customer event, we can see this number.
We just want to drag in our health to give.
And just wrap up here.
I look forward to it.
And this will convert the float into an integer.
Then if we just hook this up here and go compile and go play, we can test this out.
So let me get damaged twice.
I got damaged three times.
And let's say I pick up this help.
It should fill up two hearts.
So I picked up the heart and it filled up two hearts.
So I just wanted to add that to make the health pick up a bit more dynamic.